#### Contact

justleslied@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/lesliedeshotel-rambo-25b0784a (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Nursing ACLS BLS

# Leslie Deshotel Rambo

PNP-PC, MNSc, CCRN - UAMS NICU

Little Rock Metropolitan Area

### Summary

Certified Pediatric Nurse Practitioner- Primary Care, MNSc, CCRN

2012-Current: RNIII at UAMS NICU, actively gaining experience in providing the specialized care required by the preterm infant and its family. Our NICU team works closely with the labor and delivery ward to ensure the most expedient care possible is provided for the at risk neonate.

Active participant in EBP and unit/hospital based QI projects. BLS, PALS, NRP, CCRN and STABLE certified, member of local chapter Sigma Theta Tau, ACCN, and NAPNAP.

Currently serving as Junior Legislative officer for ArNAPNAP. The addition of junior officers was decided upon this year as a way to involve and encourage recent APRN graduates and current APRN students in the legislative process as it effects the future of our scope of practice and also the impact of legislative decisions on Nursing as a whole.

Experienced in preemie/neonatal stabilization and preemie/neonatal PICC line placement.

1999-2012: RNIII at Arkansas Children's Hospital in the Heart Center. Experienced in the care of the patient and family congenital cardiac defects, surgical palliation, ECMO, VADs, Berlin Heart, Heart Transplants, centrifugal VADs, and Syncardia VADs. Part time nurse Preceptor and Mentor for CVICU. Previous Chair of the Unit Level Clinical Practice Council (2009-11), co-chair (2011-12), and Council Recorder (2012).

## Experience

University of Arkansas for Medical Sciences 7 years 5 months

RN III NICU April 2013 - Present (7 years 5 months) Little Rock, Arkansas Infection Control Resource RN for NICU July 2014 - June 2015 (1 year)

Served as the Infection Control Resource RN for the NICU for the past 12 months. Assisted in hand hygiene education, RSV education, Curos Cap implementation and acted as a liaison for infection control issues, as well as many other duties required by the Resource RN program including research projects and PDSA projects.

Arkansas Childrens Hospital RN III- Heart Center June 1999 - April 2012 (12 years 11 months)

Served as Chair and CoChair of Clinical Practice Council; Unit based level Level III RN in a 29 bed critical care unit where the staff specializes in the care of patients undergoing repair and palliation of congenital cardiac defects, heart transplants, Berlin Heart bridge-to-transplants, and ECMO.

St Vincent Infirmary RN II May 1995 - June 1998 (3 years 2 months)

New graduate, RN Cardiac Resource, Cardiac stepd-own, and Congestive Heart Failure outpatient clinic manager and co conceptualizer of CHF outpatient clinic program.

#### Education

University of Arkansas for Medical Sciences

Master's degree, Pediatric Nurse Practitioner · (2017 - 2019)

University of Arkansas at Little Rock
Bachelor of Science (BS), Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2011 - 2012)

University of Arkansas at Little Rock
Associate's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (1991 - 1995)